live.
Like I said, welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer where we open up with the ten
commandments that God commanded the
world to keep. Brother Tenzel, and God
spake all these words, saying, I am the
Lord thy God, which has brought thee out
of the land of Egypt, out of the house
of bondage. Thou shall have no other
gods before me. Thou shall not make unto
thee any graven image, or any likeness
of anything that is in heaven above, or
that is in the earth beneath, or that is
in the water under the earth. Thou shall
not bow down thyself to them, nor serve
them. For I the Lord thy God am a
jealous God, visiting the iniquities of
the fathers upon the children, unto the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me, and showing mercy unto
thousands of them that love me, and keep
my commandment.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain. For the Lord will not
hold him guiltless that taketh his name
in vain. Remember the Sabbath day to
keep it holy. Six days shall thou labor
and do all thy work. But the seventh day
he is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God.
In it thou shall not do any work. Thou
nor thy son, nor thy daughter, thy man's
servant, nor thy maid servant, nor thy
cattle, nor thy stranger that's within
thy gates. For six days the Lord made
heaven and earth, the sea, and all thy
inums, and rested the seventh day,
wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day, and hallowed it under thy father
and thy mother, that thy days may be
long upon the land which the Lord thy
God give thee. Thou shall not kill. Thou
shall not commit adultery. Thou shall
not steal. Thou shall not bear false
witness against thy neighbor. Thou shall
not coveret thy neighbor's house. Thou
must not cover thy neighbor's wife, nor
his man's servant, nor his maid servant,
nor his ox, nor his ass, nor anything
that is thy neighbors. We read Exodus
21-17. May the Lord have a blessing to
the reading of his words. In Jesus name
we pray. Amen. Amen.
Amen. Amen. So here on question and
answer, you can ask us a question and
we'll answer it according to the King
James Bible. And if we cannot find the
answer, we will seek further counsel to
bring you an answer at a later time. The
questions we will not answer are the
vague and the long scripture questions
as well as questions of debate. We are
not here to debate. We are here to
spread the true gospel of Jesus. So
please be as direct as possible with
your questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible. No other Bibles or
books will be acknowledged on this
program. Also, keep in mind that this is
a live stream and you may begin to send
in your questions at this time that
pertain to everlasting life. We just ask
that you keep them to a two scripture
maximum. But let me introduce you the
family that's on the panel this evening.
Brother Dre, good evening. Brother
Jerome, grace in peace. Brother Julius,
good evening everybody. Brother Tanzel,
good evening. Sister Deborah, good
evening. Brother Sean, good evening. And
we have the guest caller with us. And
I'm Brother Cornell. Please pardon me
for my technical difficulties that my
background don't look like the rest of
the family that's on here. But uh,
Sister Deborah, let us begin with our
first question of the evening. Uh, yes,
there are several held over questions
that will be answered first before
getting into tonight's
Q&A. Jennifer Love asks, "Is lighting
scented candles on the Sabbath
considering a fire like smoking on the
Sabbath?"
All right, the answer to that question
is yes. Even though the candles have a
sweet smelling scent to them, it's still
kindling a fire if using a fire to light
those candles. And those are violations
on the Lord's Sabbath day. You should
not be lighting a candle on the Lord's
Sabbath day. But let us go to Exodus the
35th chapter. Exodus
35. Because this was the Lord here
letting it be known how he wanted things
to be done. And this is Moses also here.
So let's pick it up at that verse
one. Exodus 35 and1.
And Moses gathered all the congregation
of the children of Israel together and
said unto them, these are the words
which the Lord hath commanded that ye
should do them. Six days shall work be
done, but on the seventh day there shall
be to you a holy day, a Sabbath of rest
to the Lord. So whosoever doeth work
therein shall be put to death. And the
Lord got it written all throughout his
book that this day is a holy day and he
want us to treat it as such and he want
us to rest on it as much as possible.
Now read verse three and that'll be it.
He shall kindle no fire throughout your
inhabitation upon the Sabbath day. So
Lord on the Sabbath day don't want you
to kindle no fire. You can't burn no
candles whether they sinn it or not.
Smoking is not permitted either on the
Lord's Sabbath day. So, we thank you for
that question and we also would like to
encourage you to please stop lighting
your scented candles on the Lord's
Sabbath day. And that's all I
got. And we hope that that answers your
question as as we move on to our next
one. Uh, next question. monk says in
Genesis
17:12, it mentions that Isaac was
circumcised at 8 days old. I noticed
that hospitals often perform
circumcisions the second day after
birth. Is two days acceptable or should
we wait? All right. does mention about 8
days but then they want to know about
the hospital say hey we'll do it on the
second day Julius what you say coming
out of the healthc care field
um it is normal for hospitals to
circumcise 48 hours after birth are
typically circumcised 48 hours after
birth uh in most cases but let's look at
what the book Okay, let's read that. Uh,
Tanzil, Genesis
17 and read verse 12. Noah, pick it up
at verse 11.
And ye shall circumcise the flesh of
your foreskin, and it shall be a token
of the covenant betwix me and you. So,
first of all, let's understand
circumcision is a token of the covenant.
Okay? It's a token of your faith in God
and it's token of the covenant. Go
ahead. And he that is 8 days old shall
be circumcised among you. Every manch
child in your generation, he that is
born in the house or bought with money
of any stranger which is not of thy
seed. So
now one law for all people 8 days old.
But here the thing with us we are in
captivity. I was born and raised in
Arkansas. My parents knew nothing about
circumcision. I didn't get circumcised
until we moved to Chicago and I was 17
years old. But the day that I found out
about the
circumcision, I went and scheduled
myself and I got it done. But skip down,
skip down to my brother uh skip down to
verse
24 and read it. And Abraham was 90 years
old and n when he was circumcised in the
flesh of his foreskin. When you find out
about it, the Lord made a covenant with
Abraham. And that day when he made that
covenant, he was 99 years
old. Just like verse one says, continue
to read. And Isma, his son was 13 years
old when he was circumcised in the flesh
of his foreskin. Ishmael was 13. Go
ahead. All the way to 27. Go ahead. And
the selfs same day was Abraham
circumcised and Ismael his son and all
the men of his house born in the house
and bought with money of the stranger
was circumcised with him. So his
servants were circumcised. Let's go to
the New Testament. Let's go to Acts the
16th
chapter. Acts the 16th
chapter. Israel is under the Roman
Empire and we're not self-governed now.
Acts 16 verse one we going one to three.
Go ahead and read to you. Then came he
to Derby and Lyard and behold certain
disciples was there named Timothus the
son of a certain woman which was a
Jewish and believed but his father was a
Greek. So now his wife understood and
she believed in the covenant and in the
faith of God. Go ahead. which was well
reported of by the brethren that were at
Lystra and Iconium. Continue.
Him would Paul have to go forth with him
and took and circumcised him because of
the Jews which were in those quarters.
But they knew all that his father was a
Greek. So therefore, we have to
understand. So Paul circumcised
Timothy. And notice it didn't say he was
a baby at verse one. He said he was a
disciple. So he was of age well of age.
So therefore sisters and brothers it is
when you find out about it. Now we
understand 8 days old is good once you
understand if you can arrange 8 days
old. 8 day that's good because the
eighth day represents something bigger.
It the is represents the father's
kingdom and the rolling back of flesh
which when the father's kingdom come
there will be no more flesh and blood.
Right? But it is a token. So when you
find the body and the scripture says
that uh you got to be circumcised to
take part in the
Passover, you got to be circumcised. It
is a commandment and it is necessary.
And if you don't do that, you have
broken his covenant according to Genesis
the 17th chapter. Anybody want to add to
that?
If you can get eight days,
if you can get him, if you can get the
eight days, do it. Yes. But if you
can't, like Junior say, you take it when
you can. Yep. Yep. Yeah. Two days would
be no circumcision at all. That's right.
All right. We hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next.
Moving on. Valencia asked for you to
explain 1 Corinthians 4 verse 7.
Jerome 1 Corinthians 4:7. What you say?
Let's go read
it. You get it, Tanzel. Go ahead.
1 Corinthians
4:7. But who maketh thee to defer from
another? And what hast thou that thou
didest not receive? Now if thou didest
receive it, why dost thou glory as if
thou hadest not received
it? If we go to um St. John chapter 3
verse 27, it'll it'll answer
that. Let's go
there. St. John chapter
3 verse 27.
When you get it, go ahead and read. And
John answered and said, "A man can
receive nothing except it be given him
from heaven."
And so he's saying, "So why why do we
act as though we haven't received
everything that we have, it come from
the Lord, right?" You
know, all his goodness, we know for sure
come from the Lord, you know. So, can we
tie it with that first Peter? Let's go
to first
Peter chapter 4 and we're going to read
verse 10 and
11. First Peter 4 10 and 11. You get it?
Go ahead.
If any man speak, let him speak as the
oracles of God. If any man minister, let
him do at it as the ability which God
given, that God in all things may be
glorified through Jesus Christ, to whom
be praise and dominion forever and ever.
Amen.
That's all I got on that. You know, uh
when you when you see it from the Lord,
use it to the glory of the Lord and give
God the
glory. That's all I
All right. Thank you for that. We hope
that answered your question as we move
on to our next one. Next one. Miss Way
says, "We are the Christians of the New
Testament because of the death of
Jesus." Am I right?
Yes. Cara, can you shed some light on
that? We are the Christians of the New
Testament because of the death of Jesus.
I believe that's uh Dre.
No, that's that's caller. Dre is the
next one. Go ahead.
Acts the 11th chapter
11. Read verses 25 and 26.
All right. Acts 11.
Verse 25 and 26.
Then departed Barnabas to Tarsus for to
seek Saul. And when he had found them,
he brought him unto Antioch. And it came
to pass that a whole year they assembled
themselves with the church and taught
much people and the disciples were
called Christians first in Antioch.
So you are a Christian if you are a
disciple and a disciple mean followers
right? He had follow his death and now
he have us that's following him after
his death. As far as death is
concerned, that don't make you a a
Christian
Christian what death do is if you follow
the lord you will get
salvation because we are saved by his
blood but to be a
Christian that mean that you have to
follow him. He had followers before his
death and he have us that's after his
death.
That's all I have to say. All right. We
hope that answers your question as we
move on to our next question. Next
question. Lisa asks asks, "Is there such
a thing as putting your wife or husband
away for spiritual
fornication? If there is, where is it in
the Bible? I was told this was such a
thing."
All right, Dre. Is that such a thing or
no? No, I haven't read that. But let's
go to Matthew the 5th chapter. Matthew
5, and we're going to read verses 31 and
32. Matthew 5:31 and
32. Go ahead, brother.
And it have been said, whosoever shall
put away his wife, let him give her a
right of divorcement.
But I say unto you that whosoever shall
put away his wife saving for the cause
of fornication causes her to commit
adultery and whosoever shall marry her
that he is divorced committed adultery.
So this is not talking about spiritual
adultery or fornication. This is talking
about literal
fornication. So let's go to 1
Corinthians 7. 1 Corinthians 7.
And we're going to pick it up at verse
10. 1 Corinthians 7
and10. Go ahead, brother Cornell. I
mean, uh, Tanzel,
and the Mary, I command yet not I, but
the Lord, let not the wife depart from
her
husband. But, and if she depart, let her
remain unmarried, or be reconciled to
her husband.
not, it says, "Let not the wife depart
from her
husband. And if she do
depart, let her remain unmarried or be
reconciled to her husband." Go ahead.
And let not the husband put away his
wife. And let not the husband put away
his wife. Go ahead. But to the rest
speak I, not the Lord. If any brother
have a wife that believeth not, and she
be pleased to dwell with him, let him
not put her away. So if she don't
believe, she may believe in something
else. But if she be pleased to dwell
with you, let him put her not away. Go
ahead. and the woman which have a
husband and believeth not. And if he be
pleased to dwell with her, let her not
leave him. And likewise with the husband
uh the wife. So both of them go ahead.
For the unbelieving husband is
sanctified by the wife, and the
unbelieving wife is sanctified by the
husband.
Elsewhere your children are clean, but
now are they holy.
Go ahead. But if unbelieving depart, let
them depart. A brother or sister is not
under bondage in such cases. But God
have called us to peace. If they leave
on their own, that's different. But
don't you do nothing to cause them to
want to leave. You serving the Lord. Be
a servant of the Lord. Go ahead,
brother.
But what knowest thou, oh wife, whether
thou shalt save thy husband? or how
knowest thou, oh man, whether thou shalt
save thy wife. So if you walking in the
word, maybe they'll see something in you
that they may want to latch on to it.
Who knows thou whether thou shall save
thy wife or whether thou shalt save thy
husband? So
no is the
answer. That's all I got.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
I hope that answered their
question. As we move on to our next
moving on, Alex asks, "Do you have a
sermon on Matthew 5 verse 19? Or can you
explain how the least in the kingdom
will be in the lake of fire? Isn't least
and greatest just different statuses in
the kingdom?"
All
right, Jerome, what you say?
Well, um, to answer your question, yeah,
we, the Israel of God have lessons on
it. Uh, but we're going to answer the
question for you. Let's go to that
Matthews chapter 5 and read the verse
you gave. Matthews chapter 5 verse verse
19. You mentioned different statuses in
the kingdom.
Well, one status in the kingdom that
that's referring to the least. We going
to establish what that is. And we going
to establish the status of being the
greatest in the kingdom. We talking
about we talking about the son's
kingdom. Uh, okay. So, go ahead and read
that 19.
Whosoever therefore shall break one of
the least commandments and shall teach
men so, he shall be called the least in
the kingdom of heaven.
But whosoever shall do and teach them,
the same shall be called great in the
kingdom of heaven. Yeah. So if you
happen to be great in the kingdom of
heaven, you'll be great in the son's
kingdom. You'll also be great in uh the
father's kingdom. In other words, you
going to be saved and you know inherit
the father's kingdom, too. But the least
in the kingdom, it talked about those
who breaken his commandments. There you
go. You willfully breaking his
commandments and you don't repent and
you teaching men to do the same thing.
The least in the kingdom are those
that's breaking it now. And if they
breaking it, the wages of sin is what?
Is death. If you don't repent, you'll
end up having eternal death. Okay. So
now let's go
to the uh Hebrews chapter 10.
See, it'll tell you where that those
that break his
commandment going to end up if they
don't repent. Hebrews 10, chapter 10.
Um, pick it up at 15, skip to verse
26. When you get it, go ahead. Hebrews
10 and 26. Uh, Hebrews 10, pick it up at
15 and then we'll skip to 26. Okay.
Whereof the Holy Ghost also is a witness
to us. For after that he had said
before.
Uh keep reading. Keep reading. This is
the covenant that I will make with them
after those days said the Lord. I will
put my laws into their hearts and in
their minds will I write them. Yeah. And
their sins and iniquities will I
remember no more. Yes. So under this
under the new covenant, the Lord want us
to keep his commandments. But if you
teaching men don't keep them and you
willfully breaking them, skip down to
that verse 26 and read it to the 27.
But if we willfully after that we have
received the knowledge of the truth.
Read it. Read it again. You left out a
key word. Read it again. My back. But if
we sin willfully after that we have
received the knowledge of the truth.
There were made of no more sacrifice for
sins. Mhm. But a certain fearful looking
for of judgment and fiery indignation
which shall devour the adversaries.
Mhm. See, if you sin willfully, he let
you know you going to be put in that
fire, you going to be judged. And the
Lord going to put you in the lake of
fire. That's the fiery indignation. Now,
where is this lake of fire going to be
located?
At the coming of the Lord, we gonna
establish the location of the lake of
fire. All right? And this is why uh we
say that the lake of fire is the least
of the kingdom going to be put in there.
Now, let's find out where that lake of
fire going to
be. Zechariah 14 and pick it up at uh
16. Read to the 17. We gonna tie that
with Isaiah Tanzel.
Okay. Uh Zechariah 14. Yep. Verse 16 and
17.
Okay. Go ahead and read when you get it.
And it shall come to pass that everyone
that is left of all the nations which
came against Jerusalem shall even go up
from year to year to worship the King,
the Lord of Hosts, and to keep the feast
of tabernacles.
And it shall be that whoso will not come
up of all the families of the earth unto
Jerusalem to worship the king, the Lord
of hosts, even upon them shall be no
rain. All right? So this when the Lord
come back, right? He going to be in
Jerusalem. And the people that are left
after the first resurrection, all the
stuff that happened and the Lord set up
in
Jerusalem, people got to come up from
year to year and keep his commandments
and feast of tabernacle. Now, let's go
to Isaiah 66 and 20. Tied with Isaiah 66
verse 22- 24.
And as the new heavens and the new earth
which I will make shall remain before
me, said the Lord, so shall your seed
and your name remain. And it shall come
to pass that from one new moon to
another, and from one Sabbath to another
shall all flesh come to worship before
me, said the Lord. We know that's in
Jerusalem. Go ahead. Mhm. They shall go
forth and look upon the carcasses of the
men that have transgressed against me,
for their worms shall not die, neither
shall their fire be quenched, and they
shall be in a whorey unto all flesh.
So send the lake of fire going to be in
Jerusalem and he going to tell them the
people that come up from year to year.
Go take a look at these men that sinned
against me and they being tormented in
the lake of fire which will be in
Jerusalem at that time when the Lord set
up in Jerusalem. That's that's all I got
on.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
And uh don't be least in the kingdom
because it is a fearful thing to fall
into the hands of the living
God. All right, we hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one. Moving on. The M king says, "If
drinking blood is a sin, why would Jesus
tell us to metaphorically drink his
blood? Isn't that still wrong to even
think about?"
Right, Brother Julius? We know drinking
blood is is the saying what you say and
it on
brother. Come off mute my brother. The
book says that uh first of all Isaiah
the 45th chapter he said I the Lord
speak things that are right. Now you
said you as you asked the question and
you use the word metaphorically. That
right there should be your red flag.
Metaphoric. That mean that something
that may represent something else. Okay.
So now is drinking blood a sin? Yes.
Let's go to Leviticus the 17th chapter
and let's look at at this time when the
Lord told Israel because this was up
under animal sacrifice. If you read the
whole chapter, it's under animal
sacrifice. And then he added, don't why
are you doing that? you know, sacrifice
the devil and don't eat no
blood. Now, Leviticus 17, Leviticus 17,
and let's read verse
one. Go ahead, T. And the Lord speaking
to Moses, saying, speak unto Aaron and
to his son. That's good, brother. That's
good. Skip down to verse 10 and 11. Want
to show you that this come out of the
mouth of the Lord. Go ahead.
And whatsoever man there be of the house
of Israel or or of the stranger that
adjourned among you that eat of any man
of blood, I will even set my face
against that soul that eateth blood and
will cut him off from among his people.
Now this is the practice that the pagans
did. Okay, go ahead. For the life of the
flesh is in the blood. Uhhuh. and I have
given it to you upon the altar to make
an atonement for your souls.
Oh, the blood was for an atonement, not
to be eaten. It was for an atonement,
but that was an animal sacrifice.
Continue. For it is the blood that
maketh an atonement for your souls. Now,
let's go to Matthew the 26th
chapter and let's look
at what the blood really represents.
It was an atonement, but it could never
take away your sins. It only covered you
till Jesus came. That's why he spoke
metaphorically. Now, Matthew 26, let's
read 18 and 19, my brother T. Go ahead
and read it. And he said, "Go into the
city to such a man and say unto him, the
master said, my time is at hand. I will
keep the Passover at thy house with my
disciples." I will keep the I will keep
the Passover at your house. Go ahead.
And the disciples did as Jesus had
appointed them. And they made ready the
Passover. Now they made ready the
Passover. Skip down to verse 27 and 28.
While they was at the Passover, Jesus
took the bread and break it, which
represent his broken body. Go ahead,
brother. Read verse 27.
And he took the cup and gave thanks and
gave it to them, saying, "Drink ye all
of it, for this is my blood of the new
testament, which is shed for many for
the remission of sins." Now he said,
"For drink ye all of it." That was the
wine that was in the cup, which
represented his shed body. Why? Because
without the shedding of blood, it could
be no remission of sins. So the animal
in the Old Testament, that blood don't
eat the blood. It was for an atonement
to cover you. Now Jesus has came. Now
when he say drink my
bloodhed putting yourself up under the
Lord's covenant. It's still a blood
covenant. Go ahead, brother. For this is
my blood at 28 again. For this is my
blood of the new testament which is shed
for many for the remission of sins. So
now for the forgiveness of sins. So now
it was shed for many. The blood was shed
for many. That's why he metaphorically
he never told you how he going to tell
you to drink blood when it's a sin. No,
it represented when he would come and
you put yourself up under his shed blood
by being baptized and coming up under
the covenant. Now your sins can be taken
away or and remember no more if you walk
in righteousness, keeping his laws,
statutes, and commandments. So, no, it
wasn't wrong what he was saying. It is
wrong you when you don't have the
understanding of what he's doing, right?
That's what this was all about. I
Anybody want to add to that?
Yeah. I say one thing.
He got out of St. John. He got that out
of St. John the 6th chapter. And Jesus
told you what he was
saying. The flesh profited nothing. the
words the words that I spirit and they
are life. So you can use and that is
really a metaphor and that is to let you
know that this word that he's talking
about have to go in you in your
mind that you going to say a metaphor is
wrong and a metaphor mean to make use
something to describe something else.
Yes sir. That's all I have to
All right. Read that John 6:63. Uh uh it
is the spirit that quickenth. The flesh
profitth nothing. The words that I speak
unto you, they are spirit and they are
life. And that's what he's saying all
through the book. Eat my
words. That's metaphorically speaking.
That's what it represented. That's all I
got. Yep. And we don't have to worry
about that drinking of blood. That's
that's Dracula and all that other stuff
they put on the table for us to see and
read about. All right, hope that
answered your question as we move on to
our next. Moving on. Tina Ray asks, "Can
someone send evil spirits to attack you
like a curse or a hex?"
Dre, can someone send that evil spirit
hex and a curse upon you, brother?
I mean, if you got covered, absolutely.
I mean, they got a lot of things. You
got
uh voodoo and practice in different
places. Roman
Catholicism. You got Santaia. Uh you got
the the Haitian voodoo and African arts
and sorcery and hexes and all of those
things. But the the question is, how do
you defend yourself against those
things? So, let's go to Ephesians 6.
Let's go to Ephesians 6 and we're going
to pick it up at verse 10. Ephesians 6
and
10. Go ahead, brother. When you get it.
Finally, my brother, be strong in the
Lord, in the power of his might. That's
who's that's whose might you got to be
strong in in the his might. Be strong in
him and in the power of his might. Go
ahead, brother. But put on the whole
armor of God that you may be able to
stand against the ws of the devil. Mhm.
For be wrestling not against flesh and
blood, but against
principalities, against powers, against
the rulers of the darkness of this
world, against spiritual wickedness in
high places.
That's right. there and there's a lot of
different kinds of
wickedness that's being posed your way.
You know, even when you look at Peter,
Peter was talking to
Jesus and telling Jesus was telling
Peter about what he was going to deal
with. And then Peter said, "Not so,
Lord." And Jesus said to him, "Get thee
behind me, Satan." because he was
talking to the spirit behind
Peter and you got to see it because it's
everywhere and that spiritual wickedness
comes in all kinds of forms. Go ahead,
brother.
Wherefore take unto you the whole arm of
God that ye may be able to withstand in
the evil day and have done all to
stand. So stand therefore having your
loins girded about with truth and having
on the breastplate of righteousness.
Yeah. The book says sanctify them
through thy truth. Thy word is truth.
That's John 17. Tell you to san be
sanctified. Be set apart through the
truth. God's word is truth. This is what
you got to arm yourself up with to
withstand whatever come against you.
Otherwise, you naked. Go
ahead. Above
all, I'm sorry. And your feet shard with
the preparation of the gospel of peace.
Mhm. And above all, taking the shield of
faith, wherewith ye shall be able to
quench all the fiery darts of the
wicked.
And take the helmet of salvation and the
sword of the spirit, which is the word
of God. And that's what we need, family.
So there you have it. The the thing is
whether people come at you whatever kind
of way using whatever they use, you have
to be armed with the word of God and
walk in his
power. Be strong in the Lord and in the
power of his
might. That's all I Yeah, that's
correct. Ask the question one more time.
Read the question one more time. Yes.
The question asked, can someone send
evil spirits to attack you like a curse
or hex?
Who control the evil? Who control the
spirits? Evil or unheal? The Lord. Lord,
if the Lord don't want them to touch
you, they can't do
nothing. Okay? Lord destroyed Egypt by
sending evil angels among them. But then
that's because he the Lord had some
issue with
Egypt. Same thing he did with the
brother got God that killed his 70
brothers and evil spirit come from the
Lord and eventually kill him and all the
people that helped them from the Lord.
So now if the Lord don't allow them,
yes, to send an evil spirit upon
you, they can not. They are flesh and
blood just like you. That's all I have
to say. And on your own, you can read
numbers 22 and number 23 where Bailac
was sent and the Lord would not let him
curse Israel.
And if if they do send them among you,
then you remain faithful like Job when
he had come against him and you will
over
Yep. Absolutely.
Remember who sent Satan? The Lord did.
That's what I'm saying. Okay. Lord,
absolutely. Y All right. We hope that
answered your question as we move on
with a time check to our next one. All
right. The time is 8:10.
Alex asks, "Do you guys pre-prepare for
the questions or do you answer on the
spot and find the precepts?"
Well, we we actually we do them both
because at the end of the program, we
always say that if you have sent in some
questions that we didn't have time to
answer that we have ran out of time, we
are able to view those questions. But
also there are questions that are sent
in that we do not have time to view
because they are coming in live at that
time. But in order to be able to deal
with those questions because you're
looking at a panel that has been well
taught, let's go into Daniel the 9th
chapter, Daniel
9. And when you get there, brother, I
want you to read that verse 21 and
22. Because to answer some of these
questions, whether you are able to
pre-see them or you seeing them live,
this is also what's required too. Go
ahead. Verse
21. Go ahead, brother.
Yeah. While I was speaking in prayer,
even the man Gabriel whom I had seen in
a vision at the beginning being called
to fly swiftly touched me about the time
of the evening oblation. So this is
Daniel here when he had you know sought
out an answer from the Lord and he was
praying and verse 22 is the one that I
want. Go ahead. And he informed me and
talked with me and said, "Oh Daniel, I
am now come forth to give thee skill and
understanding." Skill and understanding.
And you have this panel here which has
some skill and understanding because
they have been well taught. But let's go
into second Timothy to second Timothy
the 2 chapter and we're going to read
one verse
there because this also helps along with
the skill and
understanding. Second Timothy 2 and when
you get there brother pick it up at that
verse 15. Go ahead.
study to show thyself approved unto God,
a workman that needeth not to be
ashamed, rightly dividing the word of
truth and rightly dividing and studying
to show y yourself approved because we
go from the Old Testament to the New
Testament, from Genesis to Revelation,
all 66 books. So these are some of the
things that's required for the panel
that you see before you this evening.
And that's all I
got. And we hope that that answered your
question as we move on to our next one.
Next question. Randy Sims asks, "When
the angel prepared the body for Jesus to
take it over? Did he take it from the
earth? Did it bear some other grain?"
All right. Asking about this body,
whether or not it beared other grain.
Guess caller.
So the first thing is Jesus said in the
10th chapter of Hebrews, he said talking
to God, thou has prepared a body for
me. I don't know what you get the angel.
And the second part and the rest of it
is we don't know because there's nothing
written in the Bible that defines how he
did it. He just said he prepared it. And
then when you go, he said he uh uh uh uh
that he took upon him the seed of
Abraham.
We don't really know how he did
it because we don't have nothing
written. That's all I have to say. All
right. Hope that answered your question
as we move on to our next one. Moving
on. Anthony Thomas asks, "Any thoughts
on the death of the Pope?
Let's open this up to the panel. Any
thoughts on the death of the pope except
for he's taking his nap like many that
have uh come before him?
No.
No. No.
All right. Look like we got three nos
there. We're going to confirm it with
that and keep moving right on along to
our next question. Moving on. K Virtuous
asked in Leviticus
23:4, "How are the feast days kept in
their seasons throughout the world if
one side of the world is in a different
season from the other or is season and
they have them in quotation mark being
referenced as the date of time the
feasts are to be kept according to the C
calculations of the new moon. So how are
the feast days kept in their seasons
throughout the world? All right, guest
caller. Can you share some light?
Doesn't mean you keep them on the date
that the Bible tell you to keep them on
and in the month that the Bible tell you
to keep it in. And all months
are are started with the new moon.
So if you say eat the Passover on the
14th day of the uh h first month and
then you keep it on the uh 12th day of
the second month, that's out of
season. Either you have what they call
communion every third or fourth Sunday.
That's out of season.
or they tell or they give you the uh uh
uh uh uh communion like the Catholic
do. That's out of season. All he's
saying is keep it in the same month that
I tell you on the date that I told
you. That's all I have to say. All
right. Hope that answered your question
there as we continue to move on.
Moving on. The M king asked, "What was
supposed to change after God flooded the
earth? If evil still continued, wouldn't
it have made more sense for God to
destroy Satan and the demons, too, so
the new world would be different?"
All
right, guest caller.
Sure, I have an answer for that.
As soon as you see God, ask
him. Well, how you going to say what
makes sense or don't make sense when God
do
something? I say you better take a check
on yourself.
Cuz they tell me you questioning what
God do and trying to say what should or
should not make sense with God. You
better check yourself out, brother, cuz
you ain't questioning us. you
God. That's the one you should ask the
question to. Don't have to say. All
right, we'll leave that there and we
going to keep moving right on along.
That's good advice for you to take heed.
Go ahead, Sister Deborah. Moving along.
Edward Barber asks, "Where is David
going to rule if Jesus is sitting on his
throne? Or is he going to be in the
father's kingdom to rule?"
All right, brother Jerome about David.
Where is he going to rule if Jesus going
to be sitting on his throne?
I think you may be misunderstanding
about what the
uh
thrones or the throne of David really
is. Okay, so let's explain something.
David's David's throne, right? Jesus
going to be sitting on that throne.
Everybody that come up in the first
resurrection going to be sitting on that
throne. Okay? And it's not a a a throne
per se where it's one seat and everybody
that's in the first resurrection sitting
in one one chair so to speak. It's it's
not like that. Okay? It's what the
throne actually represent.
Okay? And so let's go take a look at it.
Let's go to Psalms
122 and pick it up at verse just read
verse 5. And then we're going to go to
Psalms 132 after
that. Psalms
122 verse 5. Just read verse
5. When you get it, go ahead. For there
are set thrones of judgment, the thrones
of the house of David. That's plural,
ain't it?
And everybody in that first resurrection
gonna be sitting on these thrones, which
is the thrones of David. they thrones of
judgment, right? That's why he told he
said when you you come up in that first
resurrection, he going to give you power
over all the nations, right? The thrones
of David. Okay, go to that Psalms 132
and read verse
11-2. Go here when you get it. The Lord
have sworn in truth under David. he
would not turn from it. Of the fruit of
thy body will I set upon thy
throne and thy children will keep my
covenant and my testimony that I shall
teach them and their children shall also
sit upon thy throne forever more. You
see all them sitting on that same
throne. Okay? And it's not it's not that
one seat in your in your mind. You may
be thinking one seat and everybody
sitting on that one seat. No, there's
several thrones, but they the thrones of
David, right? Okay. And they the thrones
of judgment. Okay. So, now let's go to
Revelations 20 and read verse
4. Go ahead when you get it. And I saw
thrones, plural. That's right. Go ahead.
And they sat upon them, and judgment was
given unto them. And I saw the souls of
them that were beheaded for the witness
of Jesus and for the word of God and
which not and which had not worshiped
the beast, neither his image, neither
had received his mark upon their
forehead or in their hands. And they
lived and reign with Christ a thousand
years. Yeah, that's it. That's all I got
on there. If anybody want to add
something. Yeah. Hey, brother Jerome, we
know blessed and holy. Go ahead, guest
caller.
Well, that's what Jesus promised
you. Go go go into Revelation 3
chapter and read verse
21. To him that overcomemeth will I
grant to sit with me in my throne, even
as I also overcame, and am sat down with
my father in his throne.
So now he let you know that you're going
to sit with him in his throne. And so I
said in Revelation the 5th chapter said
he made us unto our gods kings and
priests and we shall reign on
earth. And also Jesus is called king of
kings. There you go.
That's right.
Yes
indeed. So praise the Lord. Praise the
Lord. All
right, we hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next
question. Uh, yes. We are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday, April the
30th,
2025. Daughter of Judah says, "I was
brought I was taught that the rapture is
not biblical." What does first
Thessalonians 4 verse1 17 mean?
Well, the you know it's funny how strong
the word rapture had been taught
throughout the generations and you can't
find it nowhere in the Bible the word
rapture. But uh the word rapture it
originated from the Latin word raptor
meaning to carry away or snatching away
or to seize or tear away. It has been
said that a theologian named John Nelson
Derby he is the one in
1830 that was saying that the rapture
was even going to be before the
tribulation. And we know that that is
false. So a lot of things tied to
rapture is false. But let's go into the
question at hand you asked about that.
First Thessalonians 4 and verse 17.
But let's pick it up at that verse 15
because we know all those that have died
and they're sleeping in the grave that
they have to come out the grave and then
they're going to meet the Lord in the
air and then they coming back down to
the earth because the Lord is going to
descend.
Verse 13. Verse 13. Let's pick it up at
that verse 13. Go right ahead, brother.
But I would not have you to be ignorant,
brethren, concerning them which are
asleep, that you sorrow not, even as
others which have no
hope. For if we believe that Jesus died
and rose again, even so them also which
sleep in Jesus will God bring with them.
Yes. And sleep here we talking about
they have died, but they are taking
their sleep, which the Lord also called
death. Go ahead. For this we say unto
you by the word of the Lord, that we
which are alive and remain unto the
coming of the Lord shall not prevent
them which are asleep. Uhhuh. For the
Lord himself shall descend from heaven
with a shout, with the voice of the
archangel, and with the trump of God,
and the dead in Christ shall rise first.
So if we see that the Lord is
descending, that he is coming down,
he'll be at the clouds and then the
people that have died and the ones that
are alive are going to meet him in the
clouds. Verse 17, then we which are
alive and remain shall be caught up
together with them in the clouds to meet
the Lord in the air. And so shall we
ever be with the Lord. Yep. and we'll
show you where we're going after we meet
him in the clouds and start coming back
down. Did you want to add something to
that? Thessalonians guess call.
No, no. You have to go to go and
complete it. He said they met him in the
air. So now associate with the Lord. And
the question is where is that? He done
left heaven and you done left the earth,
right? So where do you
Yep. and you have met him in the clouds
which is a blessing but let's go to that
uh Zechariah 14 because everybody on
this panel is looking also to meet the
Lord in the clouds but then we know
where we going from there let's go
Zechariah
14 Zechariah the 14th
chapter because everyone that got some
wisdom and knowledge this should be
their ultimate goal in
life pick it up at that verse uh one
brother and Then we going to skip down
to three. Go ahead.
Behold, the day of the Lord cometh, and
thy spoil shall be divided in the midst
of thee. So the day of the Lord cometh,
and let's see where he's coming to.
Verse three.
Then shall the Lord go forth and fight
against those nations as when he fought
in the day of battle. And his feet And
his feet shall stand at that day upon
the Mount of Olive, which is before
Jerusalem on the east. and the mount of
olive shall cleave in the midst thereof
towards the east and towards the west.
And there shall be a very great valley.
Half of the mountain shall remove toward
the north and half of it toward the
south. So when the Lord come, hey, his
feet is going to stand that day upon the
mount of olives. Same place he was
before he left us on the Mount of
Olives. and everybody that met him in
there, we coming back down with him and
we're going to help fight. And that's
going to be a fight that you don't want
to miss. You want to be in that one. And
uh skip down to verse nine. Tanzel, you
want me to read that five or no? Yeah,
you can read it. Go ahead, bro.
And ye shall flee to the valley of the
mountains, for the valley of the
mountain shall reach into Ael's. Yet ye
shall flee like as ye fled from before
the earthquake in the days of Uzziah,
king of Judah. And the Lord my God shall
come and all the saints with thee. Good
catch. I'm glad we read that, brother,
because that's after we met him in the
air. Then when he comes back down,
everybody that met him in the air is
coming back down with the Lord to help
straighten out this earth that has gone
totally crazy. Now skip down and read
that verse nine.
And the Lord shall be king over all the
earth. And in that day shall there be
one Lord and his name one. Yep. and all
them other gods that people been serving
over all these years, they won't be
around because the Lord is going to be
the king over all the earth and he gonna
set things in order or you going to be
in big trouble and that's all I got.
I want to add one more thing too. Yes
sir. to Job 19th chapter.
Job 19 and started and verse read verse
23 to uh 27.
Oh that my words were now written. Oh
that they were printed in a book that
they were graven with an iron pen and
lead in the rocks forever. Mhm. For I
know that my redeemer liveth, and that
he shall stand at the latter day upon
the earth.
And though after my skin worms destroy
this body, but yet in my flesh shall I
see God, whom I shall see for myself,
and my eyes shall behold, and not
another, though my reign be consumed
within me.
So Job is going to be one of those
that's going to be raised and beat the
Lord in the air. And where did he say he
going to his demon going to stand? Upon
the earth because everybody coming down
the earth. Like I said, no such thing as
a rapture. Just like just like the
brother said.
All right.
Okay.
All right. Thank you for that ad on
there. We hope that that answered your
question and feel free to delete the
word rapture in accordance with the
Bible as we move on to our next one.
Next one. Tyrron Blonde asks, "What does
Jeremiah 14 verse 10 mean?"
Jeremiah 14 and 10. So Julius shed some
light. Let's go there. Uh
Tenzel, what does Jeremiah 14 and 10
mean? Go ahead, Tazel. Read it.
Thus said the Lord unto his people, thus
have they loved to wander. They have not
refrained their feet. Therefore, the
Lord do not accept them, and he will now
remember their iniquities and visit
their sins.
Now, this is all about Judah's
uh rebellion and refusal to listen to
the prophets of the Lord by repenting
and turning from following uh doing evil
and following strange
gods. Let's go and see why the Lord is
upset with it uh with his people.
Jeremiah the 25th chapter, pick it up at
verse
one. Remember the Lord said, "I'm going
to visit you." Go ahead. Was that
Jeremiah 25 25? Yes. Jeremiah
25:1 and two and then we going to skip
the word that came to Jeremiah
concerning all the people of Judah in
the fourth year of Jehookim the son of
Josiah king of Judah that was the first
year of Nebuchadnezzar king of Babylon.
Uhhuh. the which Jeremiah the prophet
spake unto all the people of Judah and
to all the inhabitants of Jerusalem,
saying, Now verse skip uh skip all the
way down to verse four. Well, could read
verse uh three.
From the 13th year of Josiah, the son of
Amar, king of Judah, even unto this
day, that is the three and 20th year,
the word of the Lord had come unto me,
and I have spoken unto you, rising early
and speaking, but you have not
hearkened. That's that's number one. You
have not hearkened. Go ahead.
And the Lord hath sent unto you all his
servants to prophet, rising early and
sending them, but ye have not hearkened,
nor inclined your ear to hear. That's
number two. You have not hearkened. I'm
sending my prophets, and you ain't
heard. Go ahead.
And they said, "Turn ye again now,
everyone, from his evil way, and from
the evil of your doing, and dwell in the
land that the Lord hath given unto you,
and to your fathers forever and ever."
Go ahead. And go not after other gods to
serve them, and to worship them, and
provoke me not to anger with the works
of your hands, and I will do you no
hurt. So we love to serve other people's
god like Christmas and Easter and so on
and so forth. And the Lord say don't do
this. Don't do this. This is pagan.
Don't follow out the other nations. But
we from that day to this day we still
haven't hearkened. So I'mma visit you.
How? Verse 9. And that'll be all.
Behold, I will send and take all the
families of the north, sayeth the Lord,
and Nebuchadnezzar, the king of Babylon,
my servant, and will bring them against
this land, and against the inhabitants
thereof, and against all these nations
round about, and will utterly destroy
them, make them an astonishment, and a
hissing, and a perpetual desolation.
And that's what happened.
Nebuchadnezzar, the first gentile world
ruler, came and destroyed uh uh Judah
and Jerusalem and took him captive into
Babylon. Three times he did that. Israel
was already gone under the hand of the
Assyrians and we would not listen. Even
though we saw the example, we would not
listen. Love to wander after what? Other
pagan gods would in turn wouldn't
repent. So the Lord said, "I'mma have
I'mma have you taken out your land and
you going to be destroyed and other
thing that happened to us." That's all I
got.
Yes, sir. Told us he was a jealous God,
didn't he, Julius? He said, "Don't do He
told you right there. He said, "Do
provoke me to anger and I will do you no
hurt."
Yep. Yep. So, all right. Thank you for
that, brother. Hope that answered their
question. As we move on to our next one,
moving on. Harold Peter says, "Where the
66 harmonized with each other from
Genesis to
Revelation, the so-called lost books do
not. There may be some truth to them,
but lies are wrapped around the truth as
the tree of knowledge of good and evil."
question. Does this apply to the death
sea scrolls also? Yeah, the Dead Sea
Scrolls.
Yes. Why don't we uh open this up to the
panel and um share some light from
there.
Yes, it applies to the Dead Sea Scrolls
also because uh I have many books and
one of them among them I have to find it
and dig it up is the Dead Sea Scrolls
and what's written in the Dead Sea
Scrolls. One of the things errors that
was written in the Dead Sea Scroll is
that the reason that the Lord would
allow David to build a temple because of
the blood on his hand was the blood of
Uriah Hittite that she chief of husb
But the blood uh King James version
wasn't talking about
that all because he said you shed much
blood because David and his walls killed
a lot of people but the Dead Sea Scroll
want to make it look like he's he
couldn't build a temple because he
killed Uran the
Hittite and there and I can't remember
all of it but that's a whole lot of
other stuff I read in the Dead Sea
Scrolls are just simply wrong and
there's
inside King James version.
Yep. Yeah. And hey, believe us, these 66
books in this King James is enough to
practice for a lifetime and so much
more. All right, we're going to leave it
there and we'll keep moving on to our
next question. Moving on. Altery butt
says, "I have read Exodus 36 about
kindling fire on Sabbath. My question is
the microwave, the coffee maker, the
crock pot, things that run by
electricity. Is it technically kindling
the fire? Since you don't have to gather
wood to make the fire, you just push the
button." And isn't that a personal
decision? And where does it say it's a
law or commandment?
Somebody each one of those things are
burning you. Go ahead. Uh gas caller.
Go and find what the Lord tell you when
when to see bake.
Exodus Exodus 16.
What? Go ahead. We talk about season.
Exodus 16.
when they was in the wilderness. Yep,
that's it.
Uh yeah, verse 23. Yeah.
Okay. Go ahead, Jenzel.
Um you pick it up on 22.
Okay, we'll do. Go ahead, brother. And
it came to pass that on the sixth day
they gathered twice as much bread, two
for one man. And all the rulers of the
congregation came and told Moses. And he
said unto them, this is that which the
Lord had said. Tomorrow is the rest of
the holy Sabbath unto the Lord. So bake
that which ye will bake today, and see
it that ye will seek, and that which
remainth overlay up for you to keep
until the morning.
And they laid it up until the morning as
Moses bae, and it did not sting, neither
was there any worms
therein. And Moses said, "Eat that
today, for today is a Sabbath unto the
Lord, and today you shall not find it in
the fields."
Now, when did the Lord say, "Bake it and
cease it."
The sixth day. Yep.
So where is it
written that the only place you can bake
or see something is with fire? Can't you
do it with
a microwave? Microwave. Yes, sir.
Indeed, you can cook a whole chicken in
a microwave.
Uh-huh. And and and what other thing he
said? Did he mention? Coffee maker.
Coffee making electric pots.
pot.
Right. So when did the Lord said do it?
On the sixth day, right? Yeah.
Okay. Now he says a personal thing. Sure
it is. Your personal salvation is in
your hand. You can do what God say and
get into the g good side of the kingdom
or you can do what you personally feel
and end up in the lake of fire. That's
all personal. That's all I got to say
about it.
All right, we'll leave it there as we
move on with the time. Chad,
yes, the time is 8:40. Uh, Sai Amaru
Israel asks, "Is the abomination of
desolation, the beast, and the false
prophet, the Roman Empire, or are they
three separate individuals?"
Open to the panel guest caller. We have
a book on that. Three separate
individuals.
You got a beast pocket.
Listen, you have two
beasts. One with seven head and 10 horn.
Let's go to Revelation 13th chapter and
look at it.
Pick it up at verse one.
Yeah.
And I stood upon the sand of the sea,
and saw a beast rise up out of the sea,
having seven heads and 10 horns, and
upon his horns 10 crowns, and upon his
heads the name of
blasphemy. And the beast which I saw
Go ahead. Go ahead. Finish it. And the
beast which which I saw was like unto a
leopard, and his feet were as the feet
of a bear, and his mouth as the mouth of
a lion. And the dragon gave him his
power and his seat and great authority.
Now that beast is the
nation which is called right now the
European Union.
But the other two the vast and the false
prophet are two different people. Go in
Revelation the 19th
chapter and read and start at verse 19.
This is when the Lord was
come was coming. We start at verse 11.
We going to read a little bit. 19 and
11.
And I saw heaven open, and behold, a
white horse, and he that sat upon him
was called faithful and true, and in
righteousness he do judge and make war.
and his eyes were as a flame of fire,
and on his head were many crowns. And he
had a name written that no man knew but
he himself. And he was clothed with a
vesture dipped in blood. And his name is
called the Word of God.
Go ahead. And the armies which were in
heaven follow him upon white horses
clothed in fine linen, white and clean,
and out of his mouth go.
Okay, now skip down to verse 19 and go
ahead.
And I saw the beasts and the kings of
the earth and their armies gathered
together to make war against him that
sat on the horse and against his army.
And the beast was taken, and with him
the false prophet that wrought miracles
before him, with which he deceived them
that had received the mark of the beast,
and them that worship his image. These
both were cast alive into the lake of
fire burning with brimstone.
So now you had the man beast and also
you had the false prophet which is the
pope. These both that mean two
individuals was cast into the lake of
fire
burning brimstone. Now let's go into
Isaiah 66 chapter.
Isaiah chapter
66 and we going to bring the Lord here.
Let's pick it up at
[Music]
uh
15 come with fire. 15.
Huh? Verse 15.
Okay, start there. Then
behold, the Lord will come with fire and
with his chariots like a whirlwind to
render his anger with fury, and his
rebuke with flames of fire. For by fire
and by his sword would he would the Lord
plead with all flesh, and the slaying of
the Lord shall be many. And they that
sanctify themselves and purify
themselves in the garden behind one tree
in the midst eating swine flesh and the
abomination and the mouth shall be
consumed together sayeth the Lord.
Well, I know their works and their
thoughts, and it shall come to pass that
I will gather all nations in tongues,
and they shall come and see my glory,
and I will set a sign among them.
He said he going to gather all nations
and you know in tong and they going to
come see my glory. And let me show you
what's going to happen when they come.
Skip down to verse 23. Read 23 and 24.
And it shall come to pass that from one
new moon to another and from one Sabbath
to another shall all flesh come to
worship before me, said the Lord. And
they shall go forth and look upon the
carcasses of the men that have
transgressed against me. For their worm
shall not die, neither shall their fire
be quenched, and they shall be in a
whorey unto all flesh.
Now those those two men as you where the
worms are going to be on eating on them
and the fire going to be burning them,
they won't be consumed, burnt up. Those
are the beasts and the false prophet
that Jesus going to cast into the lake
of fire when he come. And the beast the
country Jesus is going to destroy that.
That's the European Union. Cuz if you
kept
it would have told you in Revelation
that and the armies were slain with the
uh uh edge of the sword and he told all
the birds of prey and the beast to come
eat flesh. do not I don't like to use
the word
antichrist because the antichrist is
anybody that's teaches against Jesus
right Bible talks about and the false
prophet
yeah I have to say yeah that is correct
if you would like further education on
what's to come you can also purchase
this book called the four winds of
heaven it will give you a lot more
detail to a lot more things that make
you wiser
in times of the Lord. All right, we hope
that answered your question. And sister
Deborah, as time is a ticking, let's go
to our next. Moving on. Daughter of
Judah asks, "Who wrote the Apocrypher?
Why was the Apocrypher originally in the
Bible and who decided to take them out?
Why are they not considered inspired
writings?
All right, let's uh open it up to the
panel dealing with the Apocrypha.
Who said that the Apocrypha was in the
original scriptures? How could it be
when a lot the majority of the stuff
that's written in in it is in is not in
the original text?
Guess
calling. Well, the whole thing is uh uh
when you look up the proper, it will let
you know that it is not
authenticated because it's totally
contrary to the word of God. Also in an
Apocrypha, just like in the book of uh
uh uh Enoch, they talking about the
Nephilims, which angels slept with women
and had these giants and they call them
Nephilim. All that is conjecture that
was never translated from the Hebrew
writing which was Hebrew and then the
New Testament. you know uh uh uh uh at
the uh uh 12 apostles did you know they
they were some of it was
Aramaic and all these
apocryphas they was
not taken out of the books that was
written by the Israelites simple as that
and if you went in the Apocrypha and
look at it you know you'd have to be
crazy to believe some of the stuff that
they going to Hey, like you can keep
Satan together by eating some stinking
fish. You know, I guess you belch on him
and Satan will stay away from you. Give
me a break.
I know. I got an apocalypse. I got a
book of
Enoch. I have a
book. I I have the books of
Ez I got a holy command. I got all these
books. You know why? So I could read
them and debunk all of this foolishness
that people supposed to be getting out
of. And that's probably written by
Gentiles and
not
Israel. In case you didn't know it,
there's not one book in the Bible that
was written by nonIsraelites.
That's right. Apocrypha did not come was
not written by
Israelites. That's all I have to say.
All right, thank you for that light. As
we move on to our next question, moving
on. Ni Jones says in Revelation 14
verse1, it talks about the
144,000 standing on Mount Zion with the
lamb. Would it just be the
144,000 or will the multitude in
Revelation
7:9 also be in the mount Zion with the
lamb Christ?
All right, let's go to Revelation 14
and1. Open it up to the panel because
you want to know if it would only be the
144,000,
right?
So go ahead with that Tenzel and then
we'll open it up to the P.
And I looked and lo, a lamb stood on the
of the mount Zion and with him
144,000 having his father's name written
in their
foreheads and then they want to know or
will it be the multitude that's in
Revelation 7 verse9.
Let's keep reading there and let this
define about this 144th power. Yeah.
Verse two, gentlemen. And I heard a
voice from heaven as a voice of many
waters and as a voice of a great
thunder. And I heard the voice of
harpers harping with their harps. And
they sung as it were a new song before
the throne and before the four beasts
and the elders. And no man could learn
that song, but the 144,000 which were
redeemed from the earth.
Go ahead. These are they which were not
defiled with women. For they are
virgins. That mean, let me go a piece at
a time. If they weren't defiled with
women, that means that they was men.
Isn't that correct? That's right.
Go ahead.
But they are virgins. These are they
which follow the Lamb, whethersoever he
goeth. These were redeemed from among
men, being the first fruits unto God and
unto the lamb.
Now, first thing is they and and and and
said they never had no G in their mouth.
Did you read that?
And in their mouth was found no G for
they are without fault before the throne
of God. Right.
So now these person one thing they was
males because they never been defiled by
women they virgin and said they had no g
in their mouth re that they ain't never
told a lie.
They ain't nobody got grown and didn't
tell a lie. That's why Jesus was called
the holy one of Israel. Right. No. Now
read the seven part. Read the rest of
the rest. Revelation 7. Now I just want
to defi define that.
Or will the
multitude in Revelation 7
verse9 also be
with also be on Mount Zion with the lamb
Christ.
Read it. Uh so uh Revelation 7 verse9
after this I beheld in low a great
multitude which no man could number of
all nations and kindreds and people and
tongues stood before the throne and
before the land with clothes with white
robes and palms in their hands.
Now let's let's let's let's examine that
one in one in Revelation 14 was
immortals because he said they was
redeemed from the earth, didn't it?
Right?
So now that mean they was not even the
other
44,000 that was in the seventh chapter
of Revelation.
M
and you know why I know instead of just
reading that back up and read 144,000
and then get down to the number to let
you know cuz uh somebody's getting these
these 144,000 mixed up.
Uh let me start at verse one. Revelation
7.
Okay. And after these things, I saw four
angels standing on the four corners of
the earth, holding the four winds of the
earth, that the wind should not blow on
the earth, nor on the sea, nor on any
tree. And I saw another angel ascending
from the east, having the seal of the
living God. And he cried with a loud
voice to the four angels to whom it was
given to hurt the earth and the sea,
saying, "Hurt not the earth, neither the
sea, nor the trees, till we have sealed
the servants of our God," and their
forehead is. And I heard the number of
them which were sealed. And there were
sealed 140 and 4,000s of all the tribes
of the children of Israel.
Now, these the flesh and blood people
that were sealed. Now read about the uh
multitude.
After this I beheld and lo a great
multitude which no man could number of
all nations and kindreds and people in
tongues stood before the throne and
before the lamb clothed with white robes
and palms in their hands.
Go ahead read some more.
You skip down
13. Skip down because answer the
question ask what are these gun who who
are these right?
And one of the elders answered saying
unto me but what are these which are
raided in white robes and which came
they said unto him sir thou knowest and
he said to me these are they which came
out of great tribulation and have washed
their robes and made them white in the
blood of the lamb.
Now these people went through great
tribulation. Go ahead and read.
Therefore are they before the throne of
God and serve him day and night in his
temple. And he that siteth on the throne
shall dwell among them.
They shall no more, neither thirst
anymore. Neither shall the sun light on
them nor any heat. For the Lamb which is
in the midst of the throne shall feed
them, and shall lead them unto living
fountains of water. And God shall wipe
away all tears from their eyes
and let me know. And let me know they
had not been redeemed. You know why? He
say he gonna feed them and lead them
unto living waters. There you go. These
these are mortal people. Isaiah spoke
about these
people. Let's go to Isaiah the 49th
chapter and read from 8:es 8-6.
Isaiah
49. Pick it up at verse 8.
Yeah. Thus sayeth the Lord, in an
acceptable time have I heard thee. In a
day of salvation have I helped thee, and
I will preserve thee, and give thee for
a covenant for the people to establish
the earth, to cause to inherit the
desolation heritage, that that thou
mayest say to the prisoners, go forth.
To them that are in darkness, kill
yourselves. They shall feed in the
waves, and their pasture shall be in all
high places. They shall not hunger nor
thirst. Neither shall the heat nor sun
smite them. But he that have mercy on
them shall lead them, even by the
springs of water shall he guide
them. And I will make all my mountains.
Go ahead. And I will make all my
mountains a way, and my highways shall
be exalted.
So that's that's that's 16, right?
No, that's verse 11.
Go ahead. Behold, these shall come from
far. And lo, these from the north and
from the west, and these from the land
of
sinn, oh heavens, and be joyful, O
earth, and break forth into singing, oh
mountains, for the Lord have comforted
his people, and will have mercy upon his
afflicted. But Zion said, "The Lord hath
forsaken me, and my Lord hath forgotten
me." What can a woman forget her sucking
child that she should not have
compassion on the son of her womb? Yeah,
they may forget, but yet will I not
forget thee. Behold, I have great I have
graven thee upon the palms of my hands,
and thy walls are continually before me.
So now, like I said in Revelation, the
son ain't going to light on no more,
right? And they ain't going to thirst no
more hunger.
Going to leave them by fountains of
water. Revelation said rivers of water.
These are flesh and blood people. That
144,000 and that number that no man
could number of are flesh and blood
people in the seventh chapter of
Revelation. But that 144 thou,000 in the
14th chapter uh of Revelation are
immortals. Why? Because he said they was
redeemed from the earth and they all
males. And you're going to tell me ain't
the only thing going to be saved is
males. Two different 144,000
right?
One one is immortal and the rest them
and and the one in seventh chapter are
mortal along with the number that no man
could number. That's all I have to say.
All right. I hope that that answered
your question there. Sister Derer time
check. Yes. The time is 9:00.
9:00. Well, we have ran out of time. We
got one more, Cornell.
Oh, we got one more. Number eight.
Oh, okay. We really have two
more. Uh, so we can answer this one and
one more after that if we move quickly.
This question says, uh, Troy Barber
says, "Can you explain Genesis 9 verse
6."
All right, let's go to the Genesis 9 and
verse six. talking about who so shed of
a man's
blood by man shall his blood be shed.
Yeah. So read that Tanzel. Let's open it
up to the panel.
Whoso shed of man's blood by man shall
his blood be shed. For in the image of
God made he a man. So that's uh you uh
it mean what it say. If you shed a man's
blood, you kill somebody or shed a man's
blood, your blood going to be shed by
man. Let's go to Matthew the 26th
chapter and read verse 51 and 52. He
going to tell you, Jesus going to tell
you in this
way. And behold, one of them which were
with Jesus stretched out his hand and
drew his sword and struck a servant of
the high priest and smoked off his ear.
So now that was a man that was Peter,
one of the Jesus disciples when he cut
off Malchus, another man's ear. And look
what Jesus said. Go ahead. Then Jesus
said unto him, "Put up again that sword
unto his place. For all they that take
the sword shall perish with the sword."
He said it the same thing. He just made
it more plain. Right?
by if man shed man's blood by man sh
another somebody going to shed by man by
somebody else's blood going to be shed
plus is plus is also saying too mainly
is that he is not going to have an angel
come and judge you going to set up
authority on earth going to have
laws and if you murder somebody or kill
somebody then you're going to be tried
by man and you going to be killed
by man right by hang electric chair
squad lethal lethal injection firing
squad
gas chamber he going he going to leave
that in the hand of man he ain't going
to send no angel to kill the murderer he
going to let man convict and kill the
murderer
okay thank you yeah okay sister okay
Yes. One more from most love want to
know how can I prove the tree of
knowledge of good and evil was Satan? Is
there another
verse? So they want to know how can I
prove the tree of knowledge of good and
evil was Satan? Is there another verse?
We read Isaiah 66. One behind in the
midst behind one's tree. Can we do uh
what Ezekiel 28? Would that would that
do it?
Yeah, we um let's go there. You're
right, Julius. It did say that in Isaiah
66. Where you want to go in Ezekiel,
bro?
Well, talks about Satan being in the
garden evening.
Oh, yeah. Isaiah 20 uh Ezekiel 28. Yep.
11 to uh 17 one but four beings in the
garden of Eden. Adam, Eve, Satan, and
the Lord, right? The Lord is the tree of
life, metaphorically speaking. And Satan
is a tree of the knowledge of good and
evil. He knows good, but he turned evil.
Okay. Well, I tell you what, let's read
that. Go ahead. Did somebody else say
something? Read Ezekiel.
Ezekiel. Yeah. Let's Let's go to Ezekiel
28. we there and let's pick it up um at
that verse 11 and just read down
brother.
Moreover, the word of the Lord came to
me unto me saying, son of man, take up a
lamentation unto the king of Ty and say
unto him, thus sayeth the Lord God, thou
slest of the son, full of wisdom and
perfect in beauty. Thou hast been in
Eden the garden of God, and every
precious stone was thy covering. the
sardis, topaz, and the diamond, the
barrel and onyx, the jasper, sapphire,
the emerald, the carbarkco, and gold.
The workmanship of thy tabs and of the
and of thy pipes was prepared in thee in
the day that thou was created. And thou
are the anointed chair that coverth. And
I have set thee so. And thou was upon
the holy mountain of God. And thou hast
walked up and down in the midst of the
stones of fire. And thou was perfect in
thy ways from the day that thou was
created till iniquity was found in thee.
And by the multitude of thy
merchandise they have filled the midst
of thee with violence, and thou have
sinned. Therefore I will cast thee as
profane out of the mountain of God. that
would destroy the old covering chair
from the midst of the stones of fire.
And let you know, like we said earlier,
there were two but four people in the uh
individuals in the Garden of Eden. There
was uh uh Adam and Eve, Jesus before he
became Jesus, for he is the tree of
life. And
also Satan, the devil, which is also
called the tree of the knowledge of good
and evil. and also the serpent. Both of
them are one and the same, right?
All right. So, we're going to end it on
that question. Remember that the truth
shall set you free.
If you submitted a question and we
didn't have a chance to get to it,
please don't resubmit it. Sister
Deborah, take it, put it in rotation,
and we'll deal with that question next
week. But we want to say until we all
come together again, be safe, be
blessed, stay prayed up, and may the
Lord have mercy on us all. As brother
Tanzel closes us out, our Father, which
are in heaven, hallowed be thy name, thy
kingdom come, thy will be done in earth
as it is in heaven. Give us this day our
daily bread. And forgive us of our debts
as we forgive our debt to and lead us
not into temptation but deliver us from
evil. For thine is the kingdom and the
power and the glory forever. In Jesus
name we pray. Amen.